[{"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338ee6", "question": "What is another name for a quaver?", "answer": "An eighth note", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5c62b8540ae4aacefc17eee0", "question": "Who are the Pines twins in the TV show \"Gravity Falls\"?", "answer": "Dipper and Mabel", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339de6", "question": "What seminal L.A. punk band was discovered by Ray Manzarek of the Doors?", "answer": "X", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113391c3", "question": "Which year was Marilyn Monroe born?", "answer": "1926", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339b82", "question": "What instrument was Big Band leader Bennie Goodman most associated with?", "answer": "Clarinet", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c338", "question": "How fast, on average, do adult fingernails grow?", "answer": "3 millimeters per month", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bffc", "question": "What is another word for a bird watcher?", "answer": "Twitcher", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f03113388ae", "question": "How many ghosts appear to Scrooge in Dicken's \"A Christmas Carol\"?", "answer": "Four", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338f8d", "question": "Who wrote the book \"Fahrenheit 451\"?", "answer": "Ray Bradbury", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c7ab", "question": "Tornadoes are columns of air that generally come into contact with what kind of clouds?", "answer": "Cumulonimbus cloud", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b354", "question": "Joe Louis became World Champion in which year?", "answer": "1937", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fe7c5c2877e98cb977789b3", "question": "The \"Khyber Pass\" connects what two countries?", "answer": "Afghanistan and Pakistan", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fea7b1bff048f679a45abf2", "question": "Where are carpal bones found?", "answer": "Wrist", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339dff", "question": "Whose tombstone bears the inscription \"That's All Folks\"?", "answer": "Mel Blanc", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c7a4", "question": "How old was astronaut Neil Armstrong when he passed away in 2012?", "answer": "82", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c834", "question": "Seafloor spreading at midoceanic ridges is how scientists first discovered the periodic reversal of what?", "answer": "The earth's magnetic field", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339356", "question": "What actor played The Riddler in the original \"Batman\" TV series?", "answer": "Frank Gorshin", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "59049db2cf93664eb10486b0", "question": "Who met in groups of 13, also called covens?", "answer": "Witches", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b879", "question": "In which city does the Tour de France end?", "answer": "Paris", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113395ea", "question": "In The Simpsons, who said: \" Good evening, everyone, and welcome to a wonderful evening of theater and picking up after yourselves", "answer": "Principal Skinner", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "600cc3d06de0eb824d4052ee", "question": "If one is wearing a swimsuit in Florida in public, what is illegal for one to do?", "answer": "Sing", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bdf0", "question": "What fitness program did Judi Sheppard Missett create in 1969?", "answer": "Jazzercise", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113396ab", "question": "In what film did real life siblings Jake and Maggie Gyllenhaal play brother and sister onscreen?", "answer": "Donnie Darko", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133970b", "question": "What is Woody Allen's birth-name?", "answer": "Allan Stewart Konigsberg", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b5ca", "question": "Who created the operating system \"Linux\"?", "answer": "Linus Torvalds", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5a4d964408b8581f80b092a5", "question": "How old did Canada turn on July 1, 2017?", "answer": "150 years old", "category": "general"}, {"id": "60173fab44491cbd7c5a17b4", "question": "What general commanded the American Expeditionary Forces on the Western Front during World War I?", "answer": "John Joseph \"Black Jack\" Pershing GCB", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133bb12", "question": "In what year did Jimmy Buffett open his first Margaritaville restaurant?", "answer": "1985", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b96e", "question": "How many cards comprise a pack of Tarot cards?", "answer": "78", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a226", "question": "In whose memory did Puff Daddy record the song \"I'll Be Missing You\" in 1997?", "answer": "The Notorious B.I.G.", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a8bd", "question": "What two characters are sculpted on Hannibal, Missouri's Main Street?", "answer": "Tom Sawyer and Huckleberry Finn", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b690", "question": "The tuxedo got its name from what?", "answer": "A town in New York", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5ae865ac7f28483af1e7fdd1", "question": "In 2018, a meme featured what Sonic character with a Ugandan accent saying: \"Do you know the way?\"", "answer": "Knuckles", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "6015e30bfe83fe1f2a824ba5", "question": "What was unique about the Battle of the Coral Sea?", "answer": "It was fought entirely with aircraft.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339d22", "question": "What sport is the focus of the movie \"Bend It like Beckham\"?", "answer": "Soccer", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c992", "question": "Which metal has the chemical symbol \"W\"?", "answer": "Tungsten", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5e9104f5d7247dfc0fa00311", "question": "What is the symbol for iron?", "answer": "Fe", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5be57ee45415ba52ed6f0aa7", "question": "For which brand was Michael Jackson shooting a commercial for when his hair caught on fire?", "answer": "Pepsi", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339169", "question": "Who is The Friendly Ghost?", "answer": "Casper", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133caf5", "question": "What is the Latin name for parsley?", "answer": "Petroselinum crispum", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339276", "question": "What movie stars Adam Sandler and Drew Barrymore and takes place in Hawaii?", "answer": "50 First Dates", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fc25442865c716bd8505f25", "question": "At what temperature is milk pasteurized for approximately 20 to 30 minutes?", "answer": "140 F or 60 C", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a1a2", "question": "What is Ozzy Osbourne's real first name?", "answer": "John", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133ca1d", "question": "Almonds are members of what family?", "answer": "Rose", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5a162a8df01ec323f8491724", "question": "For what did Christine Jorgensen became famous in 1952?", "answer": "The first widely known person in the US to undergo a sex change operation", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5febd6af7e83c707845b216c", "question": "Where was the maiden edition of the tennis World Team Cup held?", "answer": "Jamaica", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f03113388e7", "question": "What is the longest one syllable word in the English language?", "answer": "Screeched", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5ec722c657c9fcac0ce71977", "question": "What is the name of the traditional song fans sing at the Kentucky Derby?", "answer": "\"My Old Kentucky Home\"", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe65dd01f3c0ead6880d622", "question": "According to the Bible, where was Jesus crucified?", "answer": "Golgotha", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "6015e318fe83fe1f2a824ba6", "question": "During the Battle of Midway, Japan lost what?", "answer": "Most of its aircraft carriers.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338cae", "question": "Who wrote \"Tarzan of the Apes\" in 1912?", "answer": "Edgar Rice Burroughs", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5990f4affa5fdd6dd25324e3", "question": "Bangui is the capital of which land-locked African country?", "answer": "Central African Republic", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113394f8", "question": "Who hosted \"The Daily Show\" before Jon Stewart?", "answer": "Craig Kilborn", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a94b", "question": "Prior to August 1984, Burkina Faso was known by what name?", "answer": "The Republic of Upper Volta", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339414", "question": "\"Hello, Clara?\" is the last line from what Oscar-winning film?", "answer": "Marty", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "594a64972ebb971c1417fba6", "question": "Nuuk is the capital of which country?", "answer": "Greenland", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133ba19", "question": "What football championship was first played in 1967?", "answer": "Super Bowl", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bbfb", "question": "Chuck Taylor was the first endorser of what popular brand of shoes?", "answer": "Converse All Stars", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bd67", "question": "What prayer is said ten times during each sequence of a Catholic rosary?", "answer": "Hail Mary", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133af67", "question": "Before being hanged, whose last words were \"I only regret that I have but one life to lose for my country\"?", "answer": "Nathan Hale", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5971e0b989261e916c8e09ae", "question": "What year was the restaurant chain \"Steak 'n Shake\" founded in?", "answer": "1934", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338a4b", "question": "Who wrote the novel \"The Chocolate War\"?", "answer": "Robert Cormier", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133aaf1", "question": "What is the capital of Kyrgyzstan?", "answer": "Bishkek", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5ab99bbc21a8909e5c332d2f", "question": "What novel was the 1988 film \"Who Framed Roger Rabbit\" loosely based on?", "answer": "Who Censored Roger Rabbit?", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "6015de7afe83fe1f2a824b6b", "question": "What military leader spread Greek culture from his native Macedonia to the Indian subcontinent?", "answer": "Alexander the Great", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fea7a0cff048f679a45abe6", "question": "What part of the brain deals with hearing and language?", "answer": "Temporal lobe", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5e72cc9ed0874f1a5e2d1c24", "question": "What is Michael J. Fox\u2019s middle name?", "answer": "Andrew", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5f95aea455722f97b22684d5", "question": "Which Star Wars character is the first to be partially named after director George Lucas\u2019 son?", "answer": "Dexter Jettster", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c13b", "question": "Who said \"You'd be surprised how much it costs to look this cheap\"?", "answer": "Dolly Parton", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5feddd266ce05a3942286da1", "question": "Andy's bag that contained the stolen clothes was tied to which leg of his in the movie \"The Shawshank Redemption\"?", "answer": "Right leg", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "58be2d938faf425cf37add80", "question": "What automotive company produced car name the RX-7?", "answer": "Mazda", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113398c4", "question": "What opera, composed by John Adams, was inspired by Richard Nixon?", "answer": "Nixon in China", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe4b41c06d333868d34d6e0", "question": "Who was the famous botanist who traveled with Captain Cook on his first voyage?", "answer": "Joseph Banks", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b33e", "question": "Archbishop Makarios of Cyprus was exiled in 1956 to where?", "answer": "The Seychelles", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5ff2114f31a458464a93c440", "question": "Emily Bronte\u2019s \"Wuthering Heights\" famously described which English naturescape?", "answer": "Yorkshire moorlands", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fe6a8b720565ad31a57c7fa", "question": "What was the tiny pocket in jeans originally meant to store?", "answer": "Pocket watch", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339417", "question": "The 1947 movie \"The Egg and I\" spawned what film series?", "answer": "Ma & Pa Kettle", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "6015e14cfe83fe1f2a824b93", "question": "What best describes Germany\u2019s standard invasion strategy at the beginning of World War II?", "answer": "Attack with a combination of speed and overwhelming force (blitzkrieg)", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133aca1", "question": "What is the name of the first nuclear-powered submarine?", "answer": "USS Nautilus", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c4c5", "question": "What name is given to a smooth, oval hill created by glacial drift?", "answer": "Drumlin", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339c05", "question": "Whose first hit single was titled \"Stubborn Kind of Fellow\"?", "answer": "Marvin Gaye's", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "592eb087f83302ff91e4649d", "question": "What year did filming of the 1972 film \"The Godfather\" begin?", "answer": "1971", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133935b", "question": "Who played the role of Sue Ann Nivens on \"The Mary Tyler Moore Show\"?", "answer": "Betty White", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a640", "question": "Which US state is nicknamed the \"Badger State\"?", "answer": "Wisconsin", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fe907dd01dd7bf43be5e882", "question": "What is often referred to as the most slippery substance in the world?", "answer": "Polytetrafluoroethene also known as Teflon", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b63d", "question": "What is the common name for the Boeing 747?", "answer": "Jumbo Jet", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fecccbdec223966ae8f88a4", "question": "In what movie did Benedict Cumberbatch wear dentures that were an exact replica of Alan Turing's 60-year old set of false teeth?", "answer": "\"The Imitation Game\"", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339182", "question": "Who was the actor who played Charles in the movie \"Four Weddings and a Funeral\"?", "answer": "Hugh Grant", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b3a8", "question": "What was the name of Alexander the Great's famous horse?", "answer": "Bucephalas", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b829", "question": "The game \"cat's cradle\" is played using what material?", "answer": "String", "category": "general"}, {"id": "59071eeb3745b36be73039e6", "question": "Which young girl comes back to life early on in the \"Revival\" comic book series?", "answer": "Jordan Borchardt", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339853", "question": "In \"Spirited Away\", Yubabas giant baby Boh gets turned into what?", "answer": "Mouse", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338a7c", "question": "Who wrote the book \"The Power of Positive Thinking\"?", "answer": "Norman Vincent Peale", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "59049a0bcf93664eb1048697", "question": "The Queensland nut is another name for what nut?", "answer": "Macadamia", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fecc1e6ec223966ae8f886f", "question": "Who allegedly wrote the song \"Golden Years\" for Elvis Presley but ended up recording it himself?", "answer": "David Bowie", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c31b", "question": "Approximately how many kilometers are there in a nautical mile?", "answer": "1.85", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c3f9", "question": "Which joint type can be found inside the human skull?", "answer": "Suture", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fea3c76ff048f679a45ab3e", "question": "Catoptrophobia is the fear of what?", "answer": "Mirrors", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bce0", "question": "What fashion brand was co-founded by artist Bono?", "answer": "Edun", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338bb1", "question": "What are the seven deadly sins?", "answer": "Greed, Envy, Gluttony, Sloth, Lust, Pride And Wrath", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a346", "question": "What song contains the lyrics \"Whatever happened to my Transylvania twist\"?", "answer": "The Monster Mash", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "6014c993fbde8045e48466ef", "question": "What is a group of jelly fish called?", "answer": "A smack", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133975f", "question": "What two murderesses does Billy Flynn represent in Chicago?", "answer": "Velma Kelly and Roxie Hart", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339de8", "question": "What was the name of Edgar Bergen's dummy?", "answer": "Mortimer Snerd", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339e97", "question": "What movie did the villain Noah Cross appear in?", "answer": "Chinatown", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bfb0", "question": "What relation to you is your uncle's father?", "answer": "Grandfather", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b4b4", "question": "When did sharpshooter Annie Oakley die?", "answer": "1926", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bd1b", "question": "What is the only New World member of OPEC?", "answer": "Venezuela", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fd66555a5bfecdd737e085e", "question": "What was the costliest earthquake in U.S. history?", "answer": "Northridge (1994)", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133caa5", "question": "With what is charcoal and saltpeter mixed to make gunpowder?", "answer": "Sulfur", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5b7abb606490a8cc1a6e5296", "question": "How many flavors of quarks are there?", "answer": "6", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339957", "question": "What was Mrs. Addams\u2019 first name on the TV show \"The Addams Family\"?", "answer": "Morticia", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5feddc5e6ce05a3942286d9b", "question": "Which film included the real 1946 Macy\u2019s Thanksgiving Day Parade?", "answer": "\"Miracle on 34th Street\"", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fb08298cf631c2414a13b46", "question": "How many soccer players should each team typically hove on the field at the start of each match?", "answer": "11", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c15e", "question": "What is the alcoholic ingredient in a Bloody Mary?", "answer": "Vodka", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c5da", "question": "Which country deliberately introduced myxomatosis to reduce its rabbit population?", "answer": "Australia", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ace2", "question": "What was New York's Liberty Island called before its name was changed in 1956?", "answer": "Bedloe's Island", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b809", "question": "Who are the Mario Brothers usually trying to save?", "answer": "Princess Peach", "category": "general"}, {"id": "58e2f54e2e77afa695b03104", "question": "What is the capital of Maldives?", "answer": "Mal\u00e9", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5f17804eb8195c09b948d5c0", "question": "What are the suction-like cups on a gecko's toes that allows it to attach itself to any surface called?", "answer": "Setae", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133af53", "question": "During World War II, who was the \"Desert Fox\"?", "answer": "Field Marshall Rommell", "category": "history"}, {"id": "59e6b28dfb6c85e9e634ff3f", "question": "Which years did Henry VI reign England?", "answer": "1422 to 1461 and 1470 to 1471", "category": "history"}, {"id": "58f5664733a95c66dc4fe761", "question": "In which film did Orson Welles play the role of Harry Lime?", "answer": "The Third Man", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113396bd", "question": "U2's Paul Hewson is better known by which nickname?", "answer": "Bono", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fecdc45ec223966ae8f88f7", "question": "Which song did Bob Dylan write on Thanksgiving after declining a dinner invitation?", "answer": "\"Just Like a Woman\"", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c30e", "question": "The name of what household product stands for \"water displacement, formulation successful in 40th attempt?", "answer": "WD-40", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a160", "question": "When did Sid Vicious join the Sex Pistols?", "answer": "1977", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "58f5666033a95c66dc4fe762", "question": "What is the capital of Michigan?", "answer": "Lansing", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338fe2", "question": "What is the name of Lois Lane's younger sister?", "answer": "Lucy Lane", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "58f5675e33a95c66dc4fe76a", "question": "Scoleciphobia is the fear of what?", "answer": "Worms", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe65f211f3c0ead6880d635", "question": "Which President of South Africa ordered Nelson Mandela\u2019s release from prison?", "answer": "De Klerk", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b4a1", "question": "Which country hosted the first Winter Olympic Games?", "answer": "France", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338bfa", "question": "Mark Rothko is best known for his work in what genre of painting?", "answer": "Abstract", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f031133899c", "question": "The John Knowles novel \"A Separate Peace\" is narrated by which character?", "answer": "Gene", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5bb357d02627b8fe95581be5", "question": "Within the English language, what author has the most published books?", "answer": "L. Ron Hubbard", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133af06", "question": "President Gerald Ford was a member of which political party?", "answer": "Republican Party", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338dfe", "question": "What is the Roman name of the Greek god Cronus?", "answer": "Saturn", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338a07", "question": "Which Shakespeare play sees the brother of a novice nun sentenced to death for fornication?", "answer": "Measure for Measure", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c535", "question": "What children's toy started out as wallpaper cleaner?", "answer": "Play-Doh", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fea7e77ff048f679a45ac0f", "question": "Batrachophobia is the fear of what?", "answer": "Amphibians", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b3e9", "question": "What year did the Republic of South Sudan gain its independence?", "answer": "2011", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c7e1", "question": "What do SETI programs search for?", "answer": "Extraterrestrial Intelligence", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fecdcfaec223966ae8f88fb", "question": "In the film \"Goodfellas\", what airline is robbed?", "answer": "Lufthansa", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c5c0", "question": "What are female elephants called?", "answer": "Cows", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338e66", "question": "When subjects of \"Who's Who\" pass away, what companion volume do they move to?", "answer": "Who Was Who", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c6d2", "question": "What disease was once nicknamed \"the white plague\"?", "answer": "Tuberculosis", "category": "science"}, {"id": "60160173fe83fe1f2a824c5f", "question": "According to a famous Polish legend, which creature made a blanket to keep baby Jesus warm?", "answer": "A spider, which is why Poles have a great reverence for spiders.", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fef92186ce05a3942286e80", "question": "What does Paul McCartney reportedly do in the background of the Beach Boys song \"Vegetables\"?", "answer": "Munch on a celery", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b998", "question": "In the standard Monopoly game, what place will you land on if you roll 9 when on Park Avenue?", "answer": "Oriental Avenue", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5ff3cf4b4f032c0db195b490", "question": "What was a temple on the Athenian Acropolis dedicated to the goddess Athena?", "answer": "The Parthenon", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fe000ae1cf6db9ac4808d15", "question": "Which country has the oldest airport in the world that's still in operation?", "answer": "USA", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c88d", "question": "What does the Holmes and Rahe scale measure?", "answer": "Stress caused by life events", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338f13", "question": "What author created Middle-Earth?", "answer": "J. R. R. Tolkien", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fe0df12fcbed638185eaa18", "question": "What is the largest ski area in the world?", "answer": "Les Trois Vall\u00e9es, France", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fcc1aadc97eb73f6a51a26e", "question": "Which lake has the most fish species in the world?", "answer": "Lake Malawi - It is located in Africa between the countries Malawi, Mozambique and Tanzania.", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a803", "question": "What city is overlooked by a large statue named \"Christ the Redeemer\"?", "answer": "Rio de Janeiro", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "58dba1d3874c93a3298b212c", "question": "How many distinct campaigns did the Crusades have?", "answer": "Nine", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fe771a2eec85e375820b2fb", "question": "What does a flower worn behind a woman's right ear mean in Hawaii?", "answer": "She's single", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "58dba39f874c93a3298b213e", "question": "Who was nicknamed La Pucelle d'Orl\u00e9ans?", "answer": "Joan of Arc", "category": "general"}, {"id": "58c89d9d011619dd6d415487", "question": "What is the name of the giant Canadian in South Park?", "answer": "Scott", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133921f", "question": "What is the collective name for Italian-made western movies?", "answer": "Spaghetti westerns", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f0311338922", "question": "What device does Harry Potter use to track the comings and goings of people at Hogwarts castle?", "answer": "The Marauder's Map", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339b5d", "question": "Which Star Wars film introduced the character Lando Calrissian?", "answer": "The Empire Strikes Back", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5cd40d5a685cf15b733e9892", "question": "Why did the Mongolians fail to invade Japan?", "answer": "Because of a typhoon called \"kamikaze\"", "category": "history"}, {"id": "590089fbcf842fa4c4ba968e", "question": "Which band recorded the album titled \"Slippery When Wet\"?", "answer": "Bon Jovi", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "6014c748fbde8045e48466c0", "question": "What architectural event occurs at the Mayan Temple of Kukulcan?", "answer": "During the equinoxes, a shadow resembling a snake can be seen running down the Mayan Temple of Kukulcan.", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133aee1", "question": "Whom did James Earl Ray assassinate?", "answer": "Martin Luther King Jr.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338c9e", "question": "In Rudyard Kipling's \"The Jungle Book\", what type of animal was Kaa?", "answer": "A snake", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b278", "question": "During one of his famous freedom-of-speech cases, who wore an American flag to court as a diaper?", "answer": "Larry Flynt", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5ffb61365dad637d903c882e", "question": "What is the smallest country in South America?", "answer": "Suriname", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c9a0", "question": "What is -459.67 F also know as?", "answer": "Absolute Zero", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a4ab", "question": "In which city is the Taj Mahal?", "answer": "Agra", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "59f9b9bd364247bf200fb890", "question": "What kind of bones once stiffened corsets?", "answer": "Whale", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c60a", "question": "What is an alloy?", "answer": "A metal mixed with an element", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b4f8", "question": "What is better than paper in the paper, stone, scissors game?", "answer": "Scissors", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5b23aed38f1a2238a7cb2b3d", "question": "What two countries noticed that they had the same flag at the 1936 Olympics in Berlin?", "answer": "Haiti and Liechtenstein", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b33f", "question": "Which fish, previously thought to be extinct was rediscovered In 1939?", "answer": "The Coelacanth", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c73c", "question": "What part of the body is affected by tinnitus?", "answer": "Ears", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133acbe", "question": "What name was given to the leather protection cowboys wore over the front of their pants?", "answer": "Chaps", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5feba9337e83c707845b20d3", "question": "What is the scientific name of the plant used to make liquorice?", "answer": "Glycyrrhiza Glabra", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133947e", "question": "In the movie \"Legally Blonde\", what LSAT score does Elle need to get into Harvard?", "answer": "175", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "6010ca8b0775fa611bce67fa", "question": "For what category is the Charlemagne Prize awarded?", "answer": "Work toward European unification -- Awarded to projects run by persons aged 16 to 30 that promote the idea of a unified Europe.", "category": "general"}, {"id": "600a26b3e958e8c9f3127312", "question": "Which New England state produces the majority of the country\u2019s lobsters?", "answer": "Maine", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338aee", "question": "In Greek mythology, what is the name of the god of Dreams?", "answer": "Morpheus", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338b95", "question": "What comic strip sometimes features a mailman named Beasley?", "answer": "Blondie", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338a95", "question": "In ancient Greece, what river did the souls of dead people have to cross?", "answer": "Styx", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c6c1", "question": "Sigmund Freud believed a person\u2019s psyche was composed of what three components?", "answer": "Id, the ego and the super-ego", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a56b", "question": "In 1620, the Pilgrims established the Plymouth colony in which present-day US state?", "answer": "Massachusetts", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5ccf7a52b37b32637bdc44c0", "question": "What is the first foreign country you will reach if you go south from Miami, Florida.", "answer": "Cuba", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5ff51cf7ff04d658268c9320", "question": "What fraction of a person did slaves originally count as in the U.S. Constitution?", "answer": "3/5", "category": "history"}, {"id": "590721743745b36be73039f7", "question": "What year did Charles Dickens publish a novella entitled \"A Christmas Carol\"?", "answer": "1843", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "593c4bdab8198b9a2b077966", "question": "Which \"Die Hard\" film also stars Samuel L. Jackson?", "answer": "Die Hard with a Vengence", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe8b1f201dd7bf43be5e797", "question": "What does it mean to \"86\" something?", "answer": "Get rid of it", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a2b4", "question": "Who on TV played Jeeves to Hugh Laurie's Bertie Wooster?", "answer": "Stephen Fry", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133ae8d", "question": "What Mexican general led the attack against the Alamo?", "answer": "General Antonio Lopez de Santa Anna", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a7ec", "question": "Which continental South American country borders Panama?", "answer": "Colombia", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "6003988f57a0e35c43f8389c", "question": "What female surrealist did Andre Breton call \"the sorceress who left too soon\"?", "answer": "Male surrealists almost never saw female painters as capable artists.  Varo proved them wrong with her images of women.", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a870", "question": "What Canadian island was named for the father of Queen Victoria?", "answer": "Prince Edward Island", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b319", "question": "Who killed Archduke Franz Ferdinand in Sarajevo in 1914?", "answer": "Gavrilo Princip", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338a25", "question": "Whose chest contained the \"Treasure Island\" map?", "answer": "Billy Bones'", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133adb0", "question": "What modern-day conglomerate built Zero fighter planes used to bomb Pearl Harbor?", "answer": "Mitsubishi", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c914", "question": "What is the atomic number of magnesium?", "answer": "12", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c98e", "question": "What is Lepidopterology the study of?", "answer": "Moths and butterflies", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bb7b", "question": "In the 1890's, what type of cheese did a California man named David Jacks introduce?", "answer": "Monterey Jack", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338dd9", "question": "From what language did English borrow the word \"luau\"?", "answer": "Hawaiian", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fea449aff048f679a45ab90", "question": "Which animal's milk will never curdle?", "answer": "Camel", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133adb5", "question": "Michelle Bachelet was the leader of what country?", "answer": "Chile", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f03113388e1", "question": "What is the name of the first book in the \"Bourne Trilogy\"?", "answer": "The Bourne Identity", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338c6e", "question": "\"Whistler\u2019s Mother\" was the first painting by an American to be displayed at what museum?", "answer": "The Louvre", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5e5f0bafd274615ecf514530", "question": "What brand of melty cheese was first introduced to the mass market in 1928?", "answer": "Velveeta", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339456", "question": "What film earned Henry Fonda his first Oscar for Best Actor?", "answer": "On Golden Pond", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a7c1", "question": "On what continent would you find the Great Victoria Desert?", "answer": "Australia", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fea3389ff048f679a45aaef", "question": "What animal name literally means \"pig-fish\"?", "answer": "Porpoise", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bec0", "question": "On April 11, 1990, California Angel Mike Witt combined with which starter to pitch a no-hit victory?", "answer": "Mark Langston", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5ff511baff04d658268c92c9", "question": "What was the first major war campaign fought entirely by air forces?", "answer": "The\u00a0Battle of Britain -- The Royal Air Force defended the United Kingdom against attacks from the German Air Force (Luftwaffe).", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c09f", "question": "How many wine gallons does a \"half pipe\" barrel contain?", "answer": "63", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5ad7ebc7b24f84e0b9f9ffe0", "question": "Which drummer led a band called \"The Jazz Messengers\"?", "answer": "Art Blakey", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b010", "question": "Who did Abraham Lincoln replace as president?", "answer": "James Buchanan", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133ae56", "question": "During the 1920s, gangster Al Capone ruled over what city?", "answer": "Chicago", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fe6a10b20565ad31a57c79f", "question": "Which country created the official marathon length of 26.2 miles?", "answer": "United Kingdom", "category": "history"}, {"id": "59ded323ea2747c8aff16d45", "question": "What is a \"Sam Browne\"?", "answer": "Military belt", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a934", "question": "What is the only nation that shares a land border with Denmark?", "answer": "Germany", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133972a", "question": "Who played weatherman Phil Connors in the movie \"Groundhog Day\"?", "answer": "Bill Murray", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133acc4", "question": "Who was the first American in space?", "answer": "Alan Shepard", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fd66a28a5bfecdd737e0880", "question": "Where is the last remaining Blockbuster store?", "answer": "Bend, Oregon", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fea3701ff048f679a45ab12", "question": "Which Austrian psychiatrist penned \"The Interpretation of Dreams\" in 1900?", "answer": "Sigmund Freud", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ade0", "question": "Which dynasty preceded the Han Dynasty ending its rule in 207 BC?", "answer": "Qin Dynasty", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b936", "question": "What is  the first possible property purchase on Monopoly?", "answer": "Baltic Avenue", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ac74", "question": "When did the Bronze Age occur in Europe?", "answer": "Between 3600 BC to 600 BC", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f0311338877", "question": "What is the Spanish word for navy?", "answer": "Armada", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b835", "question": "What color flag is waved to indicate \"caution\" in auto racing?", "answer": "Yellow", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338ce3", "question": "What 1838 Charles Dickens novel is subtitled \"The Parish Boy's Progress\"?", "answer": "Oliver Twist", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338be0", "question": "Who wrote the Booker prize winning novel \"The Bone People\"?", "answer": "Kerry Hulme", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133afe7", "question": "Which US president was born in Tampico, Illinois?", "answer": "Ronald Reagan", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c053", "question": "Which bird is the national bird of Honduras?", "answer": "Scarlet macaw", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339ba4", "question": "What was the title of Hootie & the Blowfish's 1995 debut album?", "answer": "Cracked Rearview", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fd6660ea5bfecdd737e0864", "question": "How many breaths does an average human take each day?", "answer": "23,040", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338a55", "question": "The Hugo Awards are given for the best literature in which genre?", "answer": "Science fiction", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a98b", "question": "What city named its airport after Jomo Kenyatta?", "answer": "Nairobi", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a539", "question": "Which US state's highest mountain is Mt. Rainier?", "answer": "Washington", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f0311338963", "question": "Under what pseudonym did Charlotte Bronte first publish \"Jane Eyre\"?", "answer": "Currer Bell", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c147", "question": "How many individual stitches are on a regulation baseball ball?", "answer": "216", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5ff3c1ee4f032c0db195b47b", "question": "How many passengers were aboard the Mayflower when it set sail for the New World in 1620?", "answer": "There were 102 passengers aboard the Mayflower, and the crew is estimated to have been about 30.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5b174613bb2d29f81593b705", "question": "Rainer Kumm was a rugby player in which national team?", "answer": "Germany's", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339af1", "question": "What sporting competition was the focus of the 2007 film \"Balls of Fury\"?", "answer": "Ping Pong", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fef96266ce05a3942286e9b", "question": "What was Meryl Streep's birth name?", "answer": "Mary Louise", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133ca11", "question": "What is the fear of lice called?", "answer": "Pediculophobia", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fec8c7eec223966ae8f884b", "question": "What school did Viktor Krum go to?", "answer": "Durmstrang Institute", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fd66818a5bfecdd737e086f", "question": "What is the most widely distributed book annually?", "answer": "The IKEA catalog", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5ae863427f28483af1e7fdc9", "question": "What was the last imperial dynasty of China?", "answer": "Qing Dynasty", "category": "history"}, {"id": "596df93df0cc2631d16a3c64", "question": "With which tune, that references the Fab Four, did Joe Diffie go to #1 in in 1996?", "answer": "\"Bigger Than The Beatles\"", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133988b", "question": "Jello Biafra was the lead singer of what band?", "answer": "Dead Kennedys", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bbb4", "question": "In what year did Walt Disney World open near Orlando, Forida?", "answer": "1971", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fede5de6ce05a3942286df2", "question": "What stop-motion animated film by Tim Burton stars Johnny Depp and Helena Bonham Carter?", "answer": "\"Corpse Bride\"", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "594d06b51a1c922dd1ac64af", "question": "What's the official state sport of Alaska?", "answer": "Dog mushing", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5ff14563b0ee8c595b6d39b9", "question": "What play's full title includes \"A Trivial Comedy for Serious People\"?", "answer": "\"The Importance of Being Earnest\"", "category": "arts"}]